Cudmore	O	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
national	O	O	JJ
park	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Central	O	LOCATION	NNP
West	O	LOCATION	NNP
Queensland	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Australia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
844	O	O	CD
&	O	O	CC
nbsp	O	O	NN
;	O	O	:
km	O	O	CC
northwest	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
Brisbane	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Vergennes	B-location	LOCATION	NNS
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
northwest	O	O	JJS
quadrant	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Addison	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Vermont	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
municipality	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
bordered	O	O	VBN
by	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
towns	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Ferrisburgh	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Panton	B-location	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Waltham	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
smallest	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
Vermont	O	LOCATION	NNP
's	O	O	POS
nine	O	O	CD
cities	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
terms	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
population	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
though	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Winooski	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
covers	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
smaller	O	O	JJR
area	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
was	O	O	VBD
the	O	O	DT
first	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
chartered	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
state	B-location	O	NN
of	I-location	O	IN
Vermont	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

True	B-location	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Rusk	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Glen	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Flora	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
within	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Sandy	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Township	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Clearfield	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Stanfold	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Barron	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

St	B-location	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Martin	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Parish	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
parish	O	O	JJ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Louisiana	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
parish	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
St	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Martinville	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Premont	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Jim	O	LOCATION	NNP
Wells	O	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Shrewsbury	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Lycoming	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Peru	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
State	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
College	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
Peru	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Cle	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Elum	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Kittitas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Washington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
populated	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
western	O	O	JJ
shores	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Muskegon	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Becker	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Sherburne	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Today	O	O	NN
it	O	O	PRP
forms	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
western	O	O	JJ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
regional	O	O	JJ
unit	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Aetolia-Acarnania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
capital	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
principal	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
ancient	O	O	JJ
times	O	O	NNS
was	O	O	VBD
Stratos	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
north	O	O	JJ
side	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Acarnania	B-location	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Corinthian	O	LOCATION	NNP
Gulf	O	LOCATION	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
considered	O	O	VBN
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
region	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Epirus	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Nangar	O	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
national	O	O	JJ
park	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
located	O	O	JJ
New	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
South	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Wales	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Australia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
west	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Sydney	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Pittsburg	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Marion	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Chattanooga	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
TN	O	O	NNP
&	O	O	CC
ndash	O	O	NN
;	O	O	:
GA	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Statistical	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Area	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Pittsburg	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
home	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
National	O	O	NNP
Cornbread	O	O	NNP
Festival	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Grantsville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
second	O	O	JJ
most	O	O	RBS
populous	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Tooele	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Stratford	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
district	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
East	O	LOCATION	NNP
End	O	LOCATION	NN
of	O	LOCATION	IN
London	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
London	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Borough	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Newham	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
England	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
6	O	O	CD
miles	O	O	NNS
(	O	O	(
10	O	O	CD
&	O	O	CC
nbsp	O	O	NN
;	O	O	:
km	O	O	CC
)	O	O	)
east-northeast	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Charing	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Cross	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
East	O	LOCATION	NNP
London	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Leikanger	B-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
municipality	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Sogn	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
og	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Fjordane	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
county	O	LOCATION	NN
,	O	O	,
Norway	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
administrative	O	O	JJ
center	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Hermansverk	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
which	O	O	WDT
is	O	O	VBZ
also	O	O	RB
the	O	O	DT
administrative	O	O	JJ
center	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Sogn	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
og	I-location	O	NNP
Fjordane	I-location	O	NNP
county	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Mississippi	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Hazlehurst	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Coconut	B-location	O	NNP
Grove	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
oldest	O	O	JJS
continuously	O	O	RB
inhabited	O	O	JJ
neighborhood	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Miami	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
Miami-Dade	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Florida	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
centred	O	O	VBN
west	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
Charing	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Cross	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

South	B-location	O	NNP
Hero	I-location	O	NNP
's	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
1,631	O	O	CD
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
census	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Swan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Creek	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Saginaw	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Melbourne	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Marshall	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
should	O	O	MD
not	O	O	RB
be	O	O	VB
confused	O	O	VBN
with	O	O	IN
Melbourne	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Victoria	O	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
Australia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Farina	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Fayette	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Marion	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
counties	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
Illinois	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
only	O	O	JJ
community	O	O	NN
with	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
name	O	O	NN
``	O	O	``
Farina	B-location	PERSON	NNP
``	O	O	``
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

County	B-location	O	NNP
Sligo	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
,	O	O	,
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Ireland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Border	O	LOCATION	NNP
Region	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
province	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Connacht	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Sligo	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
County	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Council	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
local	B-location	O	JJ
authority	I-location	O	NN
for	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
noted	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
Benbulben	O	LOCATION	NNP
Mountain	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
Ireland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
’	O	O	NNP
s	O	O	VBZ
most	O	O	RBS
distinctive	O	O	JJ
natural	O	O	JJ
landmarks	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

Dili	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
free	O	O	JJ
trade	O	O	NN
zone	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
CDP	O	O	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
41,008	O	O	CD
as	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
Census	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

James	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Town	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Sweetwater	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wyoming	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Walker	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Juniata	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Carytown	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Jasper	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Taos	B-location	O	NNP
Pueblo	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
or	O	O	CC
Pueblo	O	LOCATION	NNP
de	O	LOCATION	IN
Taos	O	LOCATION	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
an	O	O	DT
ancient	O	O	JJ
pueblo	O	O	NN
belonging	O	O	VBG
to	O	O	TO
a	O	O	DT
Taos-speaking	O	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
Tiwa	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
Native	O	O	JJ
American	O	O	JJ
tribe	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Puebloan	O	O	NNP
people	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
lies	O	O	VBZ
about	O	O	IN
north	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
modern	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Taos	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
New	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Mexico	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
pueblos	O	O	NN
are	O	O	VBP
considered	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
be	O	O	VB
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
oldest	O	O	JJS
continuously	O	O	RB
inhabited	O	O	JJ
communities	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Ira	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
St	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Clair	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
English	B-location	O	NNP
Channel	I-location	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
north-west	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
France	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
England	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
much	O	O	RB
larger	O	O	JJR
island	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Guernsey	O	LOCATION	NNP
lies	O	O	VBZ
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
west	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
Jersey	O	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
south-east	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
smaller	O	O	JJR
island	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Jethou	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
just	O	O	RB
off	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
south-west	O	O	JJ
coast	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Brookings	B-location	O	NNS
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
fourth	O	O	JJ
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Dakota	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
with	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
22,056	O	O	CD
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
census	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Brookings	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
home	O	O	NN
to	O	O	TO
South	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Dakota	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
State	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
University	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
institution	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
higher	O	O	JJR
education	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
state	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Cameron	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
parish	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Cameron	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Parish	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Louisiana	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Lake	O	LOCATION	NNP
Charles	O	LOCATION	NNP
Metropolitan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Statistical	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Area	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Prairie	B-location	O	NNP
View	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Phillips	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kansas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Copeland	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
census	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
9,045	O	O	CD
;	O	O	:
it	O	O	PRP
was	O	O	VBD
the	O	O	DT
least	O	O	JJS
populous	O	O	JJ
county	B-location	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Alabama	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Eutaw	B-location	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

In	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
census	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
81.5	O	O	CD
%	O	O	NN
African-American	O	O	JJ
.	O	O	.

Vanduser	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Scott	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Federal	B-location	O	JJ
Way	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
King	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Washington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
coastal	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
within	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Seattle	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
metropolitan	I-location	O	JJ
area	I-location	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Nassau	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Lac	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
qui	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Parle	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Campbell	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	O	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Kentucky	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	O	O	NN
seats	O	O	NNS
are	O	O	VBP
Alexandria	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Newport	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Balsam	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Aitkin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Zeelandic	B-location	O	JJ
Flanders	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
,	O	O	,
Zeelandic	O	O	NNP
:	O	O	:
Zeêuws-Vlaonderen	O	O	JJ
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
southernmost	O	O	JJ
region	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
province	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Zeeland	O	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
south-western	O	O	JJ
Netherlands	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
lies	O	O	VBZ
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Western	O	LOCATION	JJ
Scheldt	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
that	O	O	WDT
separates	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
region	O	O	NN
from	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
remainder	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Zeeland	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
Netherlands	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
north	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Zeelandic	B-location	PERSON	JJ
Flanders	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
bordered	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
south	O	O	NN
by	O	O	IN
Belgium	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
Census	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
borough	O	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
19,622	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
2017	O	O	CD
ACS	O	O	NNP
Estimates	O	O	NNP
put	O	O	VBD
the	O	O	DT
borough	O	O	NN
population	O	O	NN
at	O	O	IN
20,716	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Gardner	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
home	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
Dunn	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
State	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Park	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Gardner	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Heritage	O	LOCATION	NNP
State	O	LOCATION	NNP
Park	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Lake	O	LOCATION	NNP
Wampanoag	O	LOCATION	NNP
Wildlife	O	LOCATION	NNP
Sanctuary	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
Mount	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Wachusett	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Community	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
College	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Hartwell	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
former	O	O	JJ
village	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Henry	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Delta	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Junction	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Southeast	O	LOCATION	NNP
Fairbanks	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Census	O	LOCATION	NNP
Area	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Alaska	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
a	O	O	DT
short	O	O	JJ
distance	O	O	NN
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
confluence	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Delta	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
with	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Tanana	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
which	O	O	WDT
is	O	O	VBZ
at	O	O	IN
Big	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Delta	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
about	O	O	IN
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Fairbanks	B-location	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Mazeppa	O	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
national	O	O	JJ
park	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Central	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Queensland	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Australia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
821	O	O	CD
&	O	O	CC
nbsp	O	O	NN
;	O	O	:
km	O	O	CC
northwest	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
Brisbane	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
75	O	O	CD
&	O	O	CC
nbsp	O	O	NN
;	O	O	:
km	O	O	CC
north-west	O	O	JJS
of	O	O	IN
Clermont	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Plymouth	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Rock	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Nobleboro	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
founded	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
1788	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	B-location	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Lincoln	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Maine	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Nobleboro	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
Arthur	O	PERSON	NNP
Noble	O	PERSON	NNP
's	O	O	POS
son	O	O	NN
Arthur	O	PERSON	NNP
II	O	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
town	B-location	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Drowne	O	LOCATION	NNP
claim	O	O	NN
by	O	O	IN
Shem	O	PERSON	NNP
Drowne	O	PERSON	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
1730s	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Irkutsk	B-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
;	O	O	:
Buryat	O	O	NNP
and	O	O	CC
,	O	O	,
Erhüü	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
administrative	O	O	JJ
center	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Irkutsk	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Oblast	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Russia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
cities	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
Siberia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

St	B-location	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Peter	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Fayette	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Illinois	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Smithville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Monroe	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Mississippi	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Smithville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
birthplace	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Rod	O	PERSON	NNP
Brasfield	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
a	O	O	DT
member	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Country	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Music	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Hall	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	O	ORGANIZATION	IN
Fame	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Shanor-Northvue	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Butler	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Algansee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Branch	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Hope	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Barry	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Pickerington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Fairfield	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Franklin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
counties	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
central	O	O	JJ
region	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Ohio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
suburb	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Columbus	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Pickerington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
also	O	O	RB
home	O	O	NN
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
Motorcycle	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Hall	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	I-location	ORGANIZATION	IN
Fame	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
located	O	O	VBN
at	O	O	IN
13515	O	O	CD
Yarmouth	O	O	NNP
Dr.	O	O	NNP
off	O	O	IN
Interstate	O	O	NNP
70	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

is	O	O	VBZ
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
four	B-location	O	CD
main	I-location	O	JJ
islands	I-location	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Japan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Shikoku	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
smallest	O	O	JJS
main	O	O	JJ
island	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Honshu	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
north	O	O	JJ
east	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Kyushu	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Cochran	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Morton	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Munch	B-location	LOCATION	JJ
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Pine	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Suring	B-location	O	VBG
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Oconto	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
along	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
45th	O	O	CD
parallel	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Green	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Bay	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	LOCATION	NNP
Statistical	O	LOCATION	NNP
Area	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Braddyville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Page	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Summit	B-location	O	NN
Station	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Schuylkill	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Pingree	B-location	PERSON	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
founded	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
1882	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Sheridan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Mason	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Newhalen	B-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
Nuuriileng	O	O	NNP
in	O	O	IN
Central	O	O	NNP
Alaskan	O	O	NNP
Yup'ik	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	I-location	LOCATION	CC
Peninsula	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Borough	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Alaska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Bairoil	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Sweetwater	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wyoming	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Soso	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Jones	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Mississippi	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Corteno	B-location	O	NNP
Golgi	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
;	O	O	:
Camunian	O	O	NNP
:	O	O	:
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
an	O	O	DT
Italian	B-location	O	JJ
village	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
comune	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
central	O	O	JJ
Alps	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
province	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Brescia	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Lombardy	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
northern	O	O	JJ
Italy	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Val	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Camonica	I-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Makoti	B-location	PERSON	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
founded	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
1911	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Kaskaskia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
historically	O	O	RB
important	O	O	JJ
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Randolph	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Illinois	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
major	O	O	JJ
French	B-location	O	JJ
colonial	I-location	O	NN
town	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Illinois	O	LOCATION	NNP
Country	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
18th	O	O	JJ
century	O	O	NN
its	O	O	PRP$
peak	O	O	JJ
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
about	O	O	IN
7,000	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
when	O	O	WRB
it	O	O	PRP
was	O	O	VBD
a	O	O	DT
regional	O	O	JJ
center	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Kaskaskia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
later	O	O	RB
named	O	O	VBN
as	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
capital	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
'	O	O	POS
Illinois	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Territory	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
created	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
February	O	O	NNP
3	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
1809	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Barrington	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Illinois	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Utica	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
(	O	O	(
formerly	O	O	RB
Welaunee	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Winnebago	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Hazel	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Park	I-location	PERSON	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
incorporated	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
1941	O	O	CD
and	O	O	CC
bills	O	O	NNS
itself	O	O	PRP
as	O	O	IN
``	O	O	``
The	O	O	DT
Friendly	O	O	NNP
City	O	O	NNP
``	O	O	``
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
confluence	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Skykomish	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Snohomish	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
Snoqualmie	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
rivers	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Cascade	O	O	NNP
foothills	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
about	O	O	IN
northeast	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Seattle	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Hickory	B-location	O	NNP
Withe	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
an	O	O	DT
unincorporated	O	O	JJ
community	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
suburb	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Memphis	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
Fayette	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
area	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
officially	O	O	RB
named	O	O	VBN
New	O	LOCATION	NNP
Barbadoes	O	LOCATION	NNP
Township	O	LOCATION	NNP
until	O	O	IN
1921	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
but	O	O	CC
it	O	O	PRP
was	O	O	VBD
informally	O	O	RB
known	O	O	VBN
as	O	O	IN
Hackensack	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
since	O	O	IN
at	O	O	IN
least	O	O	JJS
the	O	O	DT
18th	O	O	JJ
century	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
Census	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
43,010	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,

La	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Sal	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
northeastern	O	O	JJ
San	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Juan	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
name	O	O	NN
comes	O	O	VBZ
from	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
La	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Sal	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Mountains	O	LOCATION	NNP
which	O	O	WDT
means	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
Spanish	O	O	JJ
``	O	O	``
The	O	O	DT
Salt	O	O	NNP
``	O	O	``
.	O	O	.

Athens	B-location	LOCATION	NNS
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
Isanti	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Kodiak	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
(	O	O	(
Alutiiq	O	O	NNP
:	O	O	:
Sun'aq	O	O	NNP
;	O	O	:
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
seven	O	O	CD
communities	O	O	NNS
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
main	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
Kodiak	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Island	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kodiak	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Island	O	LOCATION	NNP
Borough	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S.	O	LOCATION	NNP
state	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Alaska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
Town	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Decatur	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
eastern	O	O	JJ
border	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Otsego	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
New	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
York	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
naval	O	O	JJ
hero	O	O	NN
Stephen	O	PERSON	NNP
Decatur	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Princeton	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Mille	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Lacs	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Richlawn	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
home	O	O	NN
rule-class	O	O	NN
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
eastern	O	O	JJ
Jefferson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kentucky	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
surrounded	O	O	VBN
by	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
larger	O	O	JJR
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
St	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Breukelen	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
(	O	O	(
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
former	O	O	JJ
municipality	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Netherlands	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
province	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Utrecht	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Wales	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Sanpete	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
December	O	O	NNP
2008	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
Wales	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
had	O	O	VBD
no	O	O	DT
stores	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
gas	O	O	NN
stations	O	O	NNS
nor	O	O	CC
stop	O	O	JJ
lights	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

Skree	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Clay	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Louis	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Sturgis	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
St	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
City	B-location	O	NNP
of	I-location	O	IN
Sturgis	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
northeast	O	O	NN
corner	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
administratively	O	O	RB
autonomous	O	O	JJ
.	O	O	.

Mitchell	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Osage	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
honor	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
John	O	PERSON	NNP
Mitchel	O	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Calhoun	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
founded	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
1856	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
sign	O	O	NN
coming	O	O	VBG
into	O	O	IN
town	O	O	NN
proudly	O	O	RB
proclaims	O	O	VBZ
that	O	O	IN
Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
has	O	O	VBZ
``	O	O	``
Everything	O	O	NNP
but	O	O	CC
a	O	O	DT
Lake.	O	O	NNP
``	O	O	``

Chambers	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNS
Estates	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
former	O	O	JJ
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Broward	O	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Florida	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
community	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
now	O	O	RB
a	O	O	DT
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Dania	O	LOCATION	NNP
Beach	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Florida	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Vilas	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Langlade	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Alabama	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Ashland	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Times	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNS
Square	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
world	O	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
most	O	O	RBS
visited	O	O	JJ
tourist	O	O	NN
attractions	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
drawing	O	O	VBG
an	O	O	DT
estimated	O	O	VBN
50	O	O	CD
million	O	O	CD
visitors	O	O	NNS
annually	O	O	RB
.	O	O	.

Frankfort	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
capital	O	O	NN
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Commonwealth	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
of	I-location	LOCATION	IN
Kentucky	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Franklin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Lyon	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
(	O	O	(
standard	O	O	JJ
abbreviation	O	O	NN
:	O	O	:
LY	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Emporia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
General	O	O	NNP
Nathaniel	O	PERSON	NNP
Lyon	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
who	O	O	WP
was	O	O	VBD
killed	O	O	VBN
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Battle	B-location	O	NNP
of	I-location	O	IN
Wilson	I-location	PERSON	NNP
's	O	O	POS
Creek	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Civil	O	O	NNP
War	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
almost	O	O	RB
entirely	O	O	RB
surrounded	O	O	VBN
by	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
City	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Industry	O	O	NNP
with	O	O	IN
only	O	O	RB
South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
El	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Monte	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
sharing	O	O	VBG
a	O	O	DT
border	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

To	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
west	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
San	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Gabriel	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
California	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Country	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Club	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Venus	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Johnson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Ellis	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
counties	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
2,960	O	O	CD
in	O	O	IN
2010	O	O	CD
(	O	O	(
2,895	O	O	CD
in	O	O	IN
Johnson	B-location	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
65	O	O	CD
in	O	O	IN
Ellis	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
)	O	O	)
.	O	O	.

Ada	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
(	O	O	(
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
General	O	O	JJ
Law	O	LOCATION	NNP
Township	O	LOCATION	NNP
within	O	O	IN
Kent	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Bellwood	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Proviso	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Cook	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Illinois	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Gregory	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Rogers	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Oklahoma	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Minden	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Sanilac	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
within	O	O	IN
Minden	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Gilmer	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
Abel	O	PERSON	NNP
P.	O	PERSON	NNP
Upshur	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
who	O	O	WP
was	O	O	VBD
U.S.	O	LOCATION	NNP
Secretary	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
State	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
during	O	O	IN
President	O	O	NNP
John	O	PERSON	NNP
Tyler	O	PERSON	NNP
's	O	O	POS
administration	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Lovell	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Big	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Horn	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wyoming	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Charter	B-location	O	NNP
Oak	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Los	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Angeles	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
California	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
approximately	O	O	RB
east	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
downtown	O	O	NN
Los	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Angeles	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Rhodes	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Marshall	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Lester	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Limestone	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Alabama	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
included	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Huntsville-Decatur	O	O	NNP
Combined	O	O	NNP
Statistical	O	O	NNP
Area	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
International	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Falls	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

A	O	O	DT
portion	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Bois	O	O	NNP
Forte	O	O	NNP
Indian	O	O	NNP
Reservation	O	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
.	O	O	.

A	O	O	DT
small	O	O	JJ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Voyageurs	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
National	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Park	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
extends	O	O	VBZ
into	O	O	IN
its	O	O	PRP$
boundary	O	O	JJ
,	O	O	,
with	O	O	IN
Lake	B-location	O	NNP
of	I-location	O	IN
the	I-location	O	DT
Woods	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
its	O	O	PRP$
northwest	O	O	JJS
.	O	O	.

Etowah	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Cleveland	O	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Oklahoma	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Nolensville	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Williamson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
Middle	O	LOCATION	NNP
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
it	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
about	O	O	IN
22	O	O	CD
miles	O	O	NNS
southeast	O	O	RB
of	O	O	IN
Nashville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Tennessee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Alpine	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
northeastern	O	O	JJ
edge	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Alpine	B-location	O	NNP
has	O	O	VBZ
been	O	O	VBN
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
many	O	O	JJ
quickly-growing	O	O	JJ
cities	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Utah	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
since	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
1970s	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
especially	O	O	RB
the	O	O	DT
1990s	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
slopes	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Wasatch	O	LOCATION	NNP
Range	O	LOCATION	NNP
north	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Highland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
American	B-location	O	NNP
Fork	I-location	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Limehouse	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
district	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
London	O	LOCATION	NNP
Borough	O	LOCATION	NNP
of	O	LOCATION	IN
Tower	O	LOCATION	NNP
Hamlets	O	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
East	O	LOCATION	NNP
London	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
east	O	O	JJ
of	O	O	IN
Charing	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Cross	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
northern	O	O	JJ
bank	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
River	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Thames	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Collyer	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Trego	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kansas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
approximately	O	O	RB
12	O	O	CD
miles	O	O	NNS
west	O	O	RB
of	O	O	IN
WaKeeney	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Luke	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Allegany	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Maryland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
located	O	O	VBN
along	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Potomac	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
just	O	O	RB
upstream	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Westernport	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Sheridan	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Madison	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Montana	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
named	O	O	VBD
after	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Civil	O	O	NNP
War	O	O	NNP
general	O	O	JJ
Philip	O	PERSON	NNP
Sheridan	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Sheridan	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
known	O	O	VBN
as	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
``	O	O	``
heart	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Ruby	O	O	NNP
Valley.	O	O	NNP
``	O	O	``

Foristell	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
St	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Charles	B-location	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Warren	B-location	PERSON	NNP
counties	O	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	O	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Jackson	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Oberlin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Decatur	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kansas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Brownsville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
home	O	O	NN
rule-class	O	O	NN
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Edmonson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Kentucky	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
just	O	O	RB
outside	O	O	JJ
Mammoth	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Cave	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
National	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Park	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Beaman	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Grundy	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Iowa	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Waterloo−Cedar	B-location	O	NNP
Falls	I-location	O	NNP
Metropolitan	O	O	NNP
Statistical	O	O	NNP
Area	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Aurora	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Wise	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Indiahoma	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Comanche	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Oklahoma	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS

Flippin	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Marion	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Arkansas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Great	B-location	O	NNP
Falls	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)

Basra	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Governorate	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
)	O	O	)
(	O	O	(
or	O	O	CC
Basra	O	LOCATION	NNP
Province	O	LOCATION	NNP
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
governorate	B-location	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
southern	O	O	JJ
Iraq	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
bordering	O	O	VBG
Kuwait	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
south	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
Iran	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
east	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Other	O	O	JJ
districts	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Basra	O	LOCATION	NNP
include	O	O	VBP
Al-Qurna	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Al-Zubair	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
Al-Midaina	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
Shatt	O	PERSON	NNP
Al-Arab	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
Abu	O	PERSON	NNP
Al-Khaseeb	O	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Al-Faw	O	O	NNP
located	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Persian	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Gulf	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Emerson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Gratiot	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Center	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Ralls	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Hannibal	B-location	O	NNP
Micropolitan	O	O	NNP
Statistical	O	O	NNP
Area	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Adrian	B-location	PERSON	JJ
Township	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Watonwan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Rio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Bravo	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Webb	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Nexø	B-location	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
sometimes	O	O	RB
spelled	O	O	VBD
Neksø	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
east	O	O	JJ
coast	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Baltic	O	O	NNP
island	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Bornholm	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Denmark	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Nexø	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
also	O	O	RB
the	O	O	DT
site	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
distillery	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
Bornholmske	O	O	NNP
Spiritfabrik	O	O	NNP
ApS	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
and	O	O	CC
a	O	O	DT
mustard	O	O	NN
factory	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
Bornholmersennep	O	O	NNP
ApS	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
also	O	O	RB
a	O	O	DT
port	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
call	O	O	NN
for	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
passenger	O	O	NN
ferries	O	O	NNS
linking	O	O	VBG
Bornholm	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
with	O	O	IN
Kołobrzeg	B-location	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
Darłowo	B-location	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
Ustka	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
Poland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Dueodde	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
beach	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
Bornholm	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Nexø	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
southeastern	O	O	JJ
corner	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
island	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Jeff	B-location	PERSON	NNP
Davis	I-location	PERSON	NNP
County	I-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Georgia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Hazlehurst	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
created	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
August	O	O	NNP
18	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
1905	O	O	CD
and	O	O	CC
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
Jefferson	O	PERSON	NNP
Davis	O	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
only	O	O	JJ
Confederate	O	O	NNP
president	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Traverse	B-location	O	NNP
City	I-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
or	O	O	CC
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S.	O	LOCATION	NNP
state	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Grand	O	LOCATION	NNP
Traverse	O	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
although	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
small	O	O	JJ
portion	O	O	NN
extends	O	O	VBZ
into	O	O	IN
Leelanau	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
21-county	O	O	JJ
Northern	O	LOCATION	NNP
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
region	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
14,674	O	O	CD
at	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
census	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
with	O	O	IN
143,372	O	O	CD
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Traverse	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
micropolitan	O	O	NNP
area	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
home	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
Tufts	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
University	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
which	O	O	WDT
has	O	O	VBZ
its	O	O	PRP$
campus	O	O	NN
along	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Medford	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Somerville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
border	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

In	O	O	IN
2017	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
Medford	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
’	O	O	NNP
s	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
grew	O	O	VBD
up	O	O	RB
to	O	O	TO
57,797	O	O	CD
residents	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

Greenville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Carolina	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

In	O	O	IN
2018	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
estimated	O	O	JJ
population	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
514,213	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
also	O	O	RB
home	O	O	NN
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
Greenville	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
County	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
School	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
District	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
largest	O	O	JJS
school	O	O	NN
system	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
South	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Carolina	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

County	O	O	NNP
government	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
headquartered	O	O	VBN
at	O	O	IN
Greenville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Square	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Byron	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Burns	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Shiawassee	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Inverness	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
southwest	O	O	JJS
shore	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Tomales	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Bay	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
northwest	O	LOCATION	JJS
of	O	LOCATION	IN
Point	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Reyes	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Station	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
at	O	O	IN
an	O	O	DT
elevation	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
43	O	O	CD
feet	O	O	NNS
(	O	O	(
13	O	O	CD
m	O	O	NN
)	O	O	)
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
community	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
after	O	O	IN
Inverness	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Scotland	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
was	O	O	VBD
named	O	O	VBN
by	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
Scottish	O	O	JJ
landowner	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Harrison	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Gloucester	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
New	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Jersey	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Lillington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Harnett	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
North	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Carolina	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Swain	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Bowling	B-location	O	VBG
Green	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Wood	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Ohio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
located	O	O	VBN
20	O	O	CD
miles	O	O	NNS
southwest	O	O	RB
of	O	O	IN
Toledo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Toledo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	LOCATION	NNP
Area	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
a	O	O	DT
member	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Toledo	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Area	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Council	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	O	ORGANIZATION	IN
Governments	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Bowling	B-location	O	VBG
Green	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
home	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Bowling	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Green	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
State	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
University	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Golden	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Golden	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Barton	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Lisbon	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Kendall	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Illinois	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Stoutsville	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Fairfield	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Ohio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Franklin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
county	O	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Blue	O	LOCATION	NNP
Ridge	O	LOCATION	NNP
foothills	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Virginia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	O	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Rocky	B-location	LOCATION	JJ
Mount	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Beaver	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Furnas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Nebraska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	O	O	JJ
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Furnas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
included	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Logan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Utah-Idaho	B-location	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
partial	O	O	JJ
)	O	O	)
Metropolitan	O	O	NNP
Statistical	O	O	NNP
Area	O	O	NNP
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
suburb	O	O	NN
or	O	O	CC
'bedroom	O	O	NN
'	O	O	''
community	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Logan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Salem	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Pierce	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
unincorporated	O	O	JJ
community	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Salem	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Moose	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Creek	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Fairbanks	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
North	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Star	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Borough	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Alaska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
'Fairbanks	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
Alaska	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Statistical	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Area	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
'	O	O	POS
.	O	O	.

Moose	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Creek	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
south	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Fairbanks	O	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Alaska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
along	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Richardson	O	LOCATION	NNP
Highway	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Chualar	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Salinas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Valley	O	LOCATION	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Monterey	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
California	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Chualar	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
southeast	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Salinas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
at	O	O	IN
an	O	O	DT
elevation	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
115	O	O	CD
feet	O	O	NNS
(	O	O	(
35	O	O	CD
m	O	O	NN
)	O	O	)
.	O	O	.

Westford	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Martin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Johnson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
for	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Blanco	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
which	O	O	WDT
traverses	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
State	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
formed	O	O	VBD
Blanco	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
1858	O	O	CD
from	O	O	IN
portions	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Burnet	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Comal	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Gillespie	B-location	PERSON	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Hays	B-location	PERSON	NNP
counties	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Blanco	B-location	PERSON	NNP
served	O	O	VBD
as	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
from	O	O	IN
1858	O	O	CD
to	O	O	TO
1890	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
when	O	O	WRB
it	O	O	PRP
was	O	O	VBD
moved	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
Johnson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

At	O	O	IN
,	O	O	,
Kenya	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
world	O	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
48th	O	O	CD
largest	O	O	JJS
country	O	O	NN
by	O	O	IN
total	O	O	JJ
area	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

With	O	O	IN
a	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
more	O	O	JJR
than	O	O	IN
52.2	O	O	CD
million	O	O	CD
people	O	O	NNS
,	O	O	,
Kenya	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
27th	O	O	JJ
most	O	O	RBS
populous	O	O	JJ
country	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Kenya	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
's	O	O	POS
capital	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Nairobi	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
while	O	O	IN
its	O	O	PRP$
oldest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
first	O	O	JJ
capital	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
coastal	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Mombasa	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Kisumu	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
City	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
third	O	O	JJ
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
also	O	O	RB
an	O	O	DT
inland	O	O	NN
port	O	O	NN
on	O	O	IN
Lake	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Victoria	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Other	O	O	JJ
important	O	O	JJ
urban	O	O	JJ
centres	O	O	NNS
include	O	O	VBP
Nakuru	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Eldoret	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Springfield	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Montgomery	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
includes	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
villages	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Wyndmoor	B-location	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
Erdenheim	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Flourtown	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
Oreland	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Plymouth	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Jefferson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Nebraska	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

As	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
2010	O	O	CD
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
Census	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
was	O	O	VBD
149,778	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
was	O	O	VBD
estimated	O	O	VBN
to	O	O	TO
be	O	O	VB
181,516	O	O	CD
in	O	O	IN
2018	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Cass	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
the	O	O	DT
most	O	O	RBS
populous	O	O	JJ
county	B-location	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
North	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Dakota	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
accounting	O	O	VBG
for	O	O	IN
nearly	O	O	RB
23	O	O	CD
%	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
state	O	O	NN
's	O	O	POS
population	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
2018	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
county	B-location	O	NN
seat	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Fargo	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
most	O	O	RBS
populous	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
state	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

New	B-location	O	NNP
Cassel	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
hamlet	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
census-designated	O	O	JJ
place	O	O	NN
(	O	O	(
CDP	O	O	NNP
)	O	O	)
in	O	O	IN
Nassau	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
New	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
York	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Murtaugh	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
rural	O	O	JJ
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Twin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Falls	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Idaho	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Twin	O	O	NNP
Falls	O	O	NNP
,	O	O	,
Idaho	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Micropolitan	O	LOCATION	NNP
Statistical	O	LOCATION	NNP
Area	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Murtaugh	B-location	PERSON	NNP
has	O	O	VBZ
existed	O	O	VBN
since	O	O	IN
at	O	O	IN
least	O	O	JJS
the	O	O	DT
early	O	O	JJ
1950s	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
named	O	O	VBN
after	O	O	IN
Mark	O	PERSON	NNP
Murtaugh	B-location	PERSON	NNP
,	O	O	,
who	O	O	WP
oversaw	O	O	VBD
a	O	O	DT
local	O	O	JJ
irrigation	O	O	NN
project	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

officially	O	O	RB
,	O	O	,
is	O	O	VBZ
one	O	O	CD
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
47	O	O	CD
prefectures	B-location	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
Japan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
has	O	O	VBZ
served	O	O	VBN
as	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Japanese	O	O	JJ
capital	O	O	NN
since	O	O	IN
1869.	O	O	CD
,	O	O	,
the	O	O	DT
Greater	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Tokyo	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Area	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
ranked	O	O	VBD
as	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
most	O	O	RBS
populous	O	O	JJ
metropolitan	O	O	JJ
area	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
both	O	O	DT
Japan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
world	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
urban	O	O	JJ
area	O	O	NN
houses	O	O	NNS
the	O	O	DT
seat	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Emperor	O	O	NNP
of	O	O	IN
Japan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Japanese	O	O	JJ
government	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
National	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Diet	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Tokyo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
formerly	O	O	RB
named	O	O	VBN
Edo	B-location	O	NNP
when	O	O	WRB
Shōgun	O	PERSON	NNP
Tokugawa	O	PERSON	NNP
Ieyasu	O	PERSON	NNP
made	O	O	VBD
the	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
his	O	O	PRP$
headquarters	B-location	O	NNS
in	O	O	IN
1603	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
became	O	O	VBD
the	O	O	DT
capital	O	O	NN
after	O	O	IN
Emperor	O	O	NNP
Meiji	O	PERSON	NNP
moved	O	O	VBD
his	O	O	PRP$
seat	O	O	NN
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
from	O	O	IN
Kyoto	O	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
1868	O	O	CD
;	O	O	:
at	O	O	IN
that	O	O	DT
time	O	O	NN
Edo	B-location	O	NNP
was	O	O	VBD
renamed	O	O	VBN
Tokyo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
Tokyo	B-location	O	NNP
Metropolis	O	O	NNP
formed	O	O	VBD
in	O	O	IN
1943	O	O	CD
from	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
merger	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
former	O	O	JJ
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
.	O	O	.

Wakeman	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Huron	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Ohio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
,	O	O	,
along	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Vermilion	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Newaygo	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
rural	O	O	JJ
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Newaygo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	O	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Cherry	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Saint	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Louis	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

North	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Baltimore	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Wood	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Ohio	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
part	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Toledo	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
OH	O	O	NNP
Metropolitan	O	O	NNP
Statistical	O	O	NNP
Area	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
member	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Toledo	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Metropolitan	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Area	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Council	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	O	ORGANIZATION	IN
Governments	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Goodwater	B-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Coosa	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Alabama	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Franklin	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Renville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Horace	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Cass	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
North	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Dakota	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Tarn	O	O	NNP
(	O	O	(
or	O	O	CC
;	O	O	:
)	O	O	)
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
department	O	O	NN
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Occitanie	O	LOCATION	NNP
region	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Southern	O	LOCATION	JJ
France	O	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Named	O	O	VBN
after	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Tarn	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
it	O	O	PRP
had	O	O	VBD
a	O	O	DT
population	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
386,448	O	O	CD
as	O	O	IN
of	O	O	IN
2016	O	O	CD
.	O	O	.

Its	O	O	PRP$
prefecture	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
largest	O	O	JJS
city	O	O	NN
is	O	O	VBZ
Albi	B-location	PERSON	NNP
.	O	O	.

Belle	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
River	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Douglas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Settlements	O	O	NNS
include	O	O	VBP
the	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
center	O	O	NN
and	O	O	CC
the	O	O	DT
village	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
East	O	LOCATION	NNP
Hebron	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Centralia	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Boone	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
county	O	LOCATION	NN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Missouri	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

A	O	O	DT
very	O	O	RB
small	O	O	JJ
portion	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
lies	O	O	VBZ
in	O	O	IN
Audrain	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

A	O	O	DT
Middle	B-location	O	NNP
River	I-location	O	NNP
Train	O	O	NNP
Station	O	O	NNP
first	O	O	RB
appeared	O	O	VBD
on	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
1877	O	O	CD
G.M	O	O	NNP
.	O	O	.

Hopkins	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
&	O	ORGANIZATION	CC
Co	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Baltimore	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Map	O	LOCATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
by	O	O	IN
1898	O	O	CD
had	O	O	VBD
a	O	O	DT
designated	O	O	VBN
Post	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Office	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
modest	O	O	JJ
street	O	O	NN
grid	O	O	NNS
.	O	O	.

Conway	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
civil	O	O	JJ
township	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Livingston	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
U.S	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

state	B-location	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Michigan	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Universal	B-location	O	NNP
City	I-location	O	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Bexar	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Texas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
borders	O	O	VBZ
San	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Antonio	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
to	O	O	TO
the	O	O	DT
northeast	O	O	NN
,	O	O	,
and	O	O	CC
is	O	O	VBZ
adjacent	O	O	JJ
to	O	O	TO
Randolph	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Air	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Force	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Base	O	ORGANIZATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Grandview	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Bayfield	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Wisconsin	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

The	O	O	DT
unincorporated	O	O	JJ
community	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Grand	O	LOCATION	NNP
View	O	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
located	O	O	VBN
in	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
of	O	O	IN
Grandview	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Pomme	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
de	I-location	LOCATION	FW
Terre	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Grant	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Eatonville	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
town	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Pierce	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Washington	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

It	O	O	PRP
is	O	O	VBZ
south	O	O	JJ
of	O	O	IN
Seattle	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
.	O	O	.

Pocopson	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
Township	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
township	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Chester	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Pennsylvania	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

Residents	O	O	NNS
of	O	O	IN
the	O	O	DT
Chesapeake	B-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Ranch	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Estates	I-location	ORGANIZATION	NNP
and	O	O	CC
Drum	B-location	O	NNP
Point	I-location	O	NNP
communities	O	O	NNS
also	O	O	RB
use	O	O	VBP
the	O	O	DT
Lusby	B-location	O	NNP
ZIP	O	O	NNP
code	O	O	NN
designation	O	O	NN
.	O	O	.

Nelson	B-location	PERSON	NNP
is	O	O	VBZ
a	O	O	DT
city	O	O	NN
in	O	O	IN
Douglas	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
Minnesota	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
,	O	O	,
United	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
States	I-location	LOCATION	NNPS
.	O	O	.

200px|right|thumb|Veterans	O	O	CD
Memorial	O	O	NNP
at	O	O	IN
Burnet	B-location	LOCATION	NNP
County	I-location	LOCATION	NNP
courthouse	O	O	NN
