Accident	O	NN	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
injury	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Pailet	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Norman	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
traffic	ORGANIZATION	NN	UNKNOWN
NOLA	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

Help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
500	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Neches	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Ave	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Arthur	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
woman	O	NN	UNKNOWN
trapped	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
attic	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
share	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

abc13eyewitness	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Public	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Schools	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Pasadena	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
closed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
until	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Sep	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
2017	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Harvey201	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
short	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
video	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
aftermath	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cotter	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Alister	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Station	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
9/3	O	CD	UNKNOWN
/	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Hill	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Creek	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Strong	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Montgomery	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tx	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
txwx	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Intense	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
category	O	NN	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
140	O	CD	UNKNOWN
+	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
mph	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
wind	O	NN	UNKNOWN
gusts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Kingwood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
4906	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Middle	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Falls	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
house	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
corner	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Millvale	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Middle	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Falls	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescu	O	NN	UNKNOWN

River	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Fry	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Road	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
CincoRanch	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
katyflood	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Sams	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Richey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
rd	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonStrong	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

RIGHT	O	RB	UNKNOWN
NOW	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
My	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
neighborhood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Cypress	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Terrace	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Spring	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Tx	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
77073	O	CD	UNKNOWN
HarveyStorm	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Pl	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Retweet	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
HARVEY	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Shelters	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
opening	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
morning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
8am	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Add	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Denver	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harbor	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
64012	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Market	O	NN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

CNN	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
MSNBC	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
FoxNews	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
A	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
useless	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
50	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Billion	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
Mexican	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Wall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
or	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Help	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
fellow	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Americans	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HOUSTON	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
vote	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
HOUSTON	LOCATION	CD	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN

Thunder	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lightning	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Rain	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
comin	O	NN	UNKNOWN
'	O	''	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
head	O	NN	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Red	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bluff	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Fairmont	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pkwy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Pasadena	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
normal	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
floods	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
area	O	NN	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
2017-08-	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
27	O	CD	UNKNOWN
10:17	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PM	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
CD	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonStrong	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Shltering	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
INFO	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
NRG	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
open	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
an	O	DT	UNKNOWN
emergency	O	NN	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
was	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
view	O	NN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
morning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Hardy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
north	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cavalcade	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
House	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
still	O	RB	UNKNOWN
ok	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	VB	UNKNOWN

People	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
saw	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
bike	O	NN	UNKNOWN
ride	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
neighborhood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
joggers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
guy	O	NN	UNKNOWN
pulling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
kayak	O	NN	UNKNOWN
towards	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Buffalo	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bayou	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
annexed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
Memorial	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonfloo	O	NN	UNKNOWN
There	O	EX	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
also	O	RB	UNKNOWN
two	O	CD	UNKNOWN
adults	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
five	O	CD	UNKNOWN
children	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
that	O	WDT	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
stuck	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
11711	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Woodshadow B-location	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	.	UNKNOWN
Pearland	O	,	UNKNOWN
,	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	,	UNKNOWN
77584	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	CD	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
very	O	RB	UNKNOWN
serious	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
will	O	MD	UNKNOWN
cause	O	VB	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
across	O	IN	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Stay	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
safe	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
roads	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
don't	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
drive	O	RB	UNKNOWN
thru	O	VB	UNKNOWN
high	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
w	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

On	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston's	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
east	O	POS	UNKNOWN
side	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Normandy	O	NN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	.	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
body	O	DT	UNKNOWN
of	O	NN	UNKNOWN
water	O	IN	UNKNOWN
for	O	NN	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
far	O	RB	UNKNOWN
as	O	RB	UNKNOWN
eye	O	IN	UNKNOWN
can	O	NN	UNKNOWN
see	O	MD	UNKNOWN
.	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Fox26	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
team	O	NN	UNKNOWN
spent	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
day	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
flooded	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
mobile	O	NN	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Vidor	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
rescued	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
cats	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
trailer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
1	O	CD	UNKNOWN
who	O	WP	UNKNOWN
was	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Rockport	O	NN	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
hit	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
130	O	CD	UNKNOWN
mph	O	NN	UNKNOWN
winds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
after	O	IN	UNKNOWN
several	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
building	O	NN	UNKNOWN
collapsed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
many	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
injured	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
high	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
school	O	NN	UNKNOWN
partial	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
need	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
21719	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Grand	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hollow	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Katy	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77450	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	VB	UNKNOWN
hel	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Um	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
it	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
looks	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
like	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cedar	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
ready	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
kill	O	VB	UNKNOWN
some	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
survivors	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
that	O	DT	UNKNOWN
military	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
machine	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Truly	O	RB	UNKNOWN
hoping	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
that	O	IN	UNKNOWN
GOP	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Congress	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
will	O	MD	UNKNOWN
fund	O	VB	UNKNOWN
rebuilding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Texas	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
Gulf	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Coast	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
rather	O	RB	UNKNOWN
than	O	IN	UNKNOWN
building	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Trump's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
bogus	O	POS	UNKNOWN
Mexico	O	NN	UNKNOWN
w	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Garth	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
road	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
IH10	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Baytown	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Tx	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Very	O	RB	UNKNOWN
High	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Baytown	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
REPORT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ON	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
harvey2017	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Austin	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
road	O	NN	UNKNOWN
closures	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
flash	O	NN	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
reported	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Austin	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flood	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
NEWS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Animals	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
trapped	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Tall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tales	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
send	O	NN	UNKNOWN
boats	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
please	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
413	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Speights	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Hankamer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77560	O	CD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

GET	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
goodies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
GIVE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Concord	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
Pine	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Caturday	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
dogsoftwitter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
running	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN

Friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
missing.	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Monika	O	.	UNKNOWN
Dobo	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tamarind	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Hill	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Martin	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
No	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
contact	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
yet	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	RB	UNKNOWN
Plz	O	.	UNKNOWN
retweet	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
MonikaDobo	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Missinginstmartin	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey201	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
one	O	CD	UNKNOWN
know	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
conditions	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
spring	O	NN	UNKNOWN
cypress	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rd	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
town	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Spring	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN

Generators	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
available	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Grainger	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Address	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
430	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Sun	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Belt	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
78408	O	CD	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Gas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
apparently	O	RB	UNKNOWN
going	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
week	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Antonio	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
because	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
it's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
still	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
90.9	O	RB	UNKNOWN
at	O	CD	UNKNOWN
the	O	IN	UNKNOWN
co-op	O	DT	UNKNOWN
on	O	NN	UNKNOWN
17th	O	IN	UNKNOWN
&	O	CD	UNKNOWN
36th	O	CC	UNKNOWN
ave	O	CD	UNKNOWN

Photos	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
On	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flowing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
across	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Autumn	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN

Trump	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
arrived	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
St	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
John's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Episcopal	O	POS	UNKNOWN
Church	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
across	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Lafayette	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
today's	O	IN	UNKNOWN
national	O	NN	UNKNOWN
day	O	POS	UNKNOWN
of	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
prayer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
flood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
2017	O	CD	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
In	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Spotts	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Waugh	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
drive	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
77007	O	CD	UNKNOWN

Unrelated	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
here's	O	RB	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
glimpse	O	DT	UNKNOWN
of	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Commerce	O	IN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bridge	O	.	UNKNOWN
history	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	,	UNKNOWN
be	O	TO	UNKNOWN
published	O	VB	UNKNOWN
in	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
upcoming	O	IN	UNKNOWN
book	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
!	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Offered	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
prayer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Patron	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
those	O	DT	UNKNOWN
impacted	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
close	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
re-entering	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
southern	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Temporary	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
reprieve	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
significant	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
time	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
slow	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
moving	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
e	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
evacuees	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
traveling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
sanantonio	O	VB	UNKNOWN
should	O	MD	UNKNOWN
check	O	VB	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
200	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Gembler	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
SATX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
WATCH	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
News	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
SA	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN

Orange	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Grove	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
awaiting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
2ND	O	CD	UNKNOWN
IMPACT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
FROM	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
WATCH	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
LIVE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
BrazoriaCounty	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
EMERGENCY	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SHELTER	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Clute	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Intermediate	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
School	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
421	O	CD	UNKNOWN
E	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Main	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Clute	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77531	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Pets	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
...	O	:	UNKNOWN

Picking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
142	O	CD	UNKNOWN
MPH	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
winds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
’	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
s	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
upper	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Headed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TXwx	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
Wheeler	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pass	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
can't	O	MD	UNKNOWN
stress	O	RB	UNKNOWN
enough	O	VB	UNKNOWN
how	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
dangerous	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
it	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
is	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
to	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
be	O	TO	UNKNOWN
out	O	VB	UNKNOWN
.	O	RP	UNKNOWN
Stay	O	.	UNKNOWN
inside	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	RB	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
going	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
basically	O	RB	UNKNOWN
park	O	VB	UNKNOWN
itself	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
over	O	RP	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
all	O	DT	UNKNOWN
weekend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
That's	O	DT	UNKNOWN
insane	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:(	O	.	UNKNOWN

Those	O	DT	UNKNOWN
who	O	WP	UNKNOWN
sought	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
refuge	O	NN	UNKNOWN
@	O	NN	UNKNOWN
1st	ORGANIZATION	CD	UNKNOWN
Baptist	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Church	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
N	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HOUSTON	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Lauder	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Aware	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
lights	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
working	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
it	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	VB	UNKNOWN
txleg	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

EdEmmett	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
need	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
21719	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Grand	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hollow	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Katy	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77450	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	VB	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
adults	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
childre	O	NN	UNKNOWN

RV	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
offers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
refuge	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
local	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Gulf	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Coast	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
evacuees	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
waters	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
continue	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
rise	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Proud	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
volunteers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
evacuating	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Luke's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
hospital	O	POS	UNKNOWN
patients	O	NN	UNKNOWN
-	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
world	O	:	UNKNOWN
class	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
planning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
-	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
so	O	:	UNKNOWN
toll	O	RB	UNKNOWN
is	O	NN	UNKNOWN
much	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
less	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	RBR	UNKNOWN
Pl	O	.	UNKNOWN
donate	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
SNRT	O	.	UNKNOWN

Safe	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
sound	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
up	O	RB	UNKNOWN
here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Dallas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
but	O	CC	UNKNOWN
praying	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
have	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
city	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
go	O	VB	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Pray	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
friends	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
We	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
will	O	MD	UNKNOWN
have	O	VB	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
long	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
road	O	NN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Right	O	RB	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Brookline	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
firefighters	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
collecting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
MDA	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Beacon	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Marys	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
wcvb	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
18107	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Flower	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Grove	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Court	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
77407	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Contact	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Delight	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
281-258-5976	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Elderly	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
diabetic	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
man	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
family	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

If	O	IN	UNKNOWN
anyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Aldine	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
area	O	NN	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
boat	O	NN	UNKNOWN
please	O	NN	UNKNOWN
go	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
425	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Shane	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Apt	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
77037	O	CD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
stuck	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
w	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
5	O	CD	UNKNOWN
pets	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
needs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
evac	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
houston	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
htx	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
5th	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
ward	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
couple	O	NN	UNKNOWN
we	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
met	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
said	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
trapped	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
church	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
3401	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Liberty	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
no	O	DT	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Hey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Louisans	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
looking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
forever	O	NN	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
hurricane	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
dog	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Contact	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
details	O	NNS	UNKNOWN

Here's	O	RB	UNKNOWN
why	O	POS	UNKNOWN
flash	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
floods	O	NN	UNKNOWN
are	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
dangerous	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
8:	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
30AM	O	CD	UNKNOWN
vs	O	:	UNKNOWN
2:30	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PM	O	NN	UNKNOWN
This	O	CD	UNKNOWN
is	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Stadium	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Road	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
facing	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
towards	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Twin	O	NN	UNKNOWN
City	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Arth	O	IN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
SOS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
area	O	NN	UNKNOWN
10ppl	O	CD	UNKNOWN
8	O	CD	UNKNOWN
addults	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
toddlers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
stuck	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
2nd	O	CD	UNKNOWN
floor	O	NN	UNKNOWN
18234	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Brightwood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
77407	O	CD	UNKNOWN

About	O	IN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
push	O	VB	UNKNOWN
past	O	RB	UNKNOWN
3.5	O	CD	UNKNOWN
"	O	``	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
rain	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cedar	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
past	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
18	O	CD	UNKNOWN
hours	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
There's	O	EX	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
LOT	O	DT	UNKNOWN
of	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
water	O	IN	UNKNOWN
that's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
about	O	WDT	UNKNOWN
to	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
head	O	IN	UNKNOWN
downstream	O	TO	UNKNOWN
.	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
think	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
Jim	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Cantore	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
may	O	MD	UNKNOWN
cry	O	VB	UNKNOWN
since	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
isn't	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
going	O	RB	UNKNOWN
to	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
hit	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
lot	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
creatures	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
displaced	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
aftermath	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
including	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Waugh	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
bridge	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
bat	O	NN	UNKNOWN
colony	O	NN	UNKNOWN

:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Send	O	NN	UNKNOWN
clothing	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
supplies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Delmar	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Stadium	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
2020	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Mangum	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Road	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
77092	O	CD	UNKNOWN

I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
could	O	MD	UNKNOWN
use	O	VB	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
new	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Playstation	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
pro	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
612	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Wharf	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Los	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Angeles	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
CA	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
9021	O	CD	UNKNOWN

We're	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
preparing	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
1,200+	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
sandbags	O	CD	UNKNOWN
for	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Houston	O	IN	UNKNOWN
schools	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
100s	O	,	UNKNOWN
more	O	CD	UNKNOWN
for	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
House	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	.	UNKNOWN

San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Felipe	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Sage	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Uptown	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
beginning	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
flood	O	VB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Not	O	RB	UNKNOWN
smart	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
drive	O	VB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	VB	UNKNOWN

River	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
street	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
front	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
pond	O	NN	UNKNOWN
forming	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
back	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
yard	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonMetro	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Katy	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Just	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
got	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
call	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
200	O	CD	UNKNOWN
beds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
open	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
evacuees	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Forge	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Families	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Shelter	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
3435	ORGANIZATION	CD	UNKNOWN
Dixie	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77021	O	CD	UNKNOWN
KHOU11	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HouNew	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Patton	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
undergone	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Search	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
efforts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
yet	O	RB	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Urban	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Search	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
Rescue	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Task	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Force	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
3	O	CD	UNKNOWN
out	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Menlo	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
received	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
orders	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
deploy	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
respond	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
…	O	VB	UNKNOWN

HoustonFlood2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflooding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
PrayForHouston	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
woman	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
children	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
rescuing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
12231	O	CD	UNKNOWN
kings	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
path	O	NN	UNKNOWN
lane	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
77044	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PrayforTexa	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Mayor	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Message	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Trailer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
'	O	POS	UNKNOWN
100	O	CD	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
percent	O	NN	UNKNOWN
'	O	''	UNKNOWN
loss	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
search	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
starts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
was	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
River	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Terrace	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
during	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
reprieve	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonweather	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Robstown	LOCATION	JJ	UNKNOWN
residents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
if	O	IN	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
sandbags	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
swing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Aviator	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ball	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
RichardMBorchardFairgrounds	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Painfully	O	RB	UNKNOWN
slow	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
movement	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
right	O	RB	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Eye	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
pounding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
;	O	:	UNKNOWN
130MPH	O	CD	UNKNOWN
+	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
winds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
coast	O	NN	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Okay	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
seen	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
someone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
asking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Lockwood	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
So	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
Minden	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooded	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
as	O	RB	UNKNOWN
well	O	RB	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey201	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Emergency	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Katy	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
22818	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Saginaw	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Point	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Katy	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Took	O	NN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
photo	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Big	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tree	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
last	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
year	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Goose	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Island	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
State	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
It's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
weathered	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
worse	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
storms	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
than	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
…	O	IN	UNKNOWN

Oh	O	UH	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
they've	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
made	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
Facebook	O	DT	UNKNOWN
now	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
if	O	RB	UNKNOWN
you	O	IN	UNKNOWN
search	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
"	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
West	O	``	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Recovery	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
"	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	``	UNKNOWN
you	O	,	UNKNOWN
can	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
help	O	MD	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
underserved	O	VB	UNKNOWN
populations	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
back	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	RB	UNKNOWN
their	O	IN	UNKNOWN
feet	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
harve	O	.	UNKNOWN

Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
photos	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
damage	O	NN	UNKNOWN
down	O	RP	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Hwy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
35	O	CD	UNKNOWN
area	O	NN	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
what	O	WP	UNKNOWN
Amber	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
looked	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
like	O	IN	UNKNOWN
when	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
rain	O	NN	UNKNOWN
stopped	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
10	O	CD	UNKNOWN
minutes	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Geez	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
RT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
view	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Ocean	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Video	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Gilbert	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
H	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Almost	O	RB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
top	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
mailboxes	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
aunts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
house	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Deer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Beltway	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Fairmont	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Parkway	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Associates	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Kuykendahl	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Louetta	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
store	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Spring	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
gave	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
customers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
reason	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
smile	O	VB	UNKNOWN
(:	O	(	UNKNOWN
tayytink	O	:	UNKNOWN
)	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	)	UNKNOWN

Gervasia	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Onezine	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
8802	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Banting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Tidwell	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
She	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
under	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
carport	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
cannot	O	MD	UNKNOWN
get	O	RB	UNKNOWN
to	O	VB	UNKNOWN
the	O	TO	UNKNOWN
roof	O	DT	UNKNOWN
346-288-0774	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
R	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Break	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
rain	O	NN	UNKNOWN
so	O	RB	UNKNOWN
went	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
check	O	VB	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
area	O	NN	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
flat	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Ferry	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Galveston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
lot	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
standing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Bray's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bayou	O	POS	UNKNOWN
water	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
level	O	NN	UNKNOWN
increasing	O	NN	UNKNOWN
dduring	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

As	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
makes	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
landfall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
quietly	O	RB	UNKNOWN
shot	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
someone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Fifth	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Avenue	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

George	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bush	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
completely	O	RB	UNKNOWN
under	O	IN	UNKNOWN
deep	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
houston	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Police	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Officers	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
working	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
tirelessly	O	RB	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
State	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
w	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
professionals	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Texans	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
…	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Allen	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Parkway	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Memorial	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Waugh	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
overpass	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Spotts	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Buffalo	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bayou	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
completely	O	RB	UNKNOWN
under	O	IN	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Horses	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
rescued	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Jefferson	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Orange	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
County	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
waiting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
groups	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
owners	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Ford	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
409Strong	O	CD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

US	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Galena	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
Residents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
cough	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
rub	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
eyes	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
pollution	O	NN	UNKNOWN
spike	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN

Oliver	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
FLOODING	O	RB	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonStrong	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
TexasFlood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Took	O	NN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
photo	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
an	O	DT	UNKNOWN
RV	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
last	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
night	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Seems	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
like	O	IN	UNKNOWN
trailers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
thrown	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
all	O	DT	UNKNOWN
around	O	IN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
sheer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wind	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

OPEN	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
SHELTER	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Church	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Project	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
295	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Sawdust	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Spring	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
77380	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Help	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Need	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
AT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
7506	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Jackrabbit	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77095	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
update	O	NN	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Looks	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
like	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Fairfield	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Inn	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

Osceola	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
County	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
nature	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
'	O	''	UNKNOWN
s	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
airboats	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
looking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
flood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
scene	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Victoria	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
can	O	MD	UNKNOWN
drive	O	VB	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
blocks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
think	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
missed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
small	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
town	O	NN	UNKNOWN
...	O	:	UNKNOWN
then	O	RB	UNKNOWN
come	O	VB	UNKNOWN
upon	O	IN	UNKNOWN
f	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HTX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
floodinghouston	O	NN	UNKNOWN
flashflooding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
reported	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Post	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Oak	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
West	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Loop	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
houston	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
7:30	O	CD	UNKNOWN
morning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

There	O	EX	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
two	O	CD	UNKNOWN
kids	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Central	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
selling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
cookies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
raise	O	VB	UNKNOWN
money	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
hurricane	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Warmed	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
heart	O	NN	UNKNOWN
nyc	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Upwind	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
side	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
wall	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
gone	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
stairwell	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Pecan	PERSON	JJ	UNKNOWN
Grove	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Fort	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bend	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
County	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Neighborhood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
was	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
3	O	CD	UNKNOWN
feet	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
underwater	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
yesterday	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
O'Connor	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hardware	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
1738	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Adams	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
selling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
plywood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
batteries	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
ect	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Employee	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
"	O	``	UNKNOWN
It's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
pretty	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
much	O	RB	UNKNOWN
first	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
come	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
,	O	NN	UNKNOWN
first	O	,	UNKNOWN
serve	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	VB	UNKNOWN
"	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	``	UNKNOWN

Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
getting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
pounded	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
eye	O	POS	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Strongest	O	.	UNKNOWN
band	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
causing	O	NN	UNKNOWN
tornado	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
warnings	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
well	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
south	O	RB	UNKNOWN
…	O	RB	UNKNOWN

San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Marcos	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
opened	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Brush	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
750	O	CD	UNKNOWN
River	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
tree	O	NN	UNKNOWN
limbs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
vegetative	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
debris	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
8am	O	CD	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
7pm	O	CD	UNKNOWN
t	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

reporting	O	NN	UNKNOWN
sustained	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
wins	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
70	O	CD	UNKNOWN
mph	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
125	O	CD	UNKNOWN
mph	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

+	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Plus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hotel	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
15701	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ten	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pl	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77084	O	CD	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
stranded	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
without	O	IN	UNKNOWN
food	O	NN	UNKNOWN
or	O	CC	UNKNOWN
clothing	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HarveyRelief	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Water	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
rising	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
..	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
need	O	NN	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
425	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Shane	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Holly	LOCATION	RB	UNKNOWN
Hall	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
RD	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
/	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Med	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ctr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
It's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
flooded	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
all	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
the	O	PDT	UNKNOWN
way	O	DT	UNKNOWN
to	O	NN	UNKNOWN
the	O	TO	UNKNOWN
highway	O	DT	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
been	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
setup	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
residents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Highlands	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
210	O	CD	UNKNOWN
N	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Magnolia	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
MORE	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
SHELTERS	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Give	O	VB	UNKNOWN
whatever	O	WDT	UNKNOWN
wall	O	DT	UNKNOWN
money	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
available	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
them	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
recover	O	VB	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
it's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
the	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
right	O	DT	UNKNOWN
thing	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	NN	UNKNOWN
do	O	TO	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
side	O	NN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
side	O	NN	UNKNOWN
comparison	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
610	O	CD	UNKNOWN
E	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Market	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
vs	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
sunny	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
day	O	NN	UNKNOWN
shows	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
how	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
catastrophic	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Hoover	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Met	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Complex	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Opens	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Its	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
Modern	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RV	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
For	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Residents	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
Evacuating	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Irma	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Helicopters	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
could	O	MD	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
searching	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
livingIn	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
@	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
West	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
loop	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
park	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN

has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
been	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
informed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
that	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Island	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Transit	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park-and-Ride	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
between	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Galveston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
League	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
City	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
will	O	MD	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
suspended	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Friday	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
8/	O	CD	UNKNOWN
25	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

STOP	O	VB	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
rumor	O	NN	UNKNOWN
mill	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
False	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
accusations	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
re	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Animal	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Shelter	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Ford	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
many	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
building	O	NN	UNKNOWN
have	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
collapsed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Volunteers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
head	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
downtown	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescues	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
launching	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonFloods	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

RESCUE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NEEDED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
FAMILY	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
WITH	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TWO	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SMALL	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
CHILDREN	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
19707	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Twin	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Canyon	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ct	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Katy	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77450	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
retweet	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonFloods	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Police	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
report	O	NN	UNKNOWN
that	O	IN	UNKNOWN
128	O	CD	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
were	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
evacuated	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Fairfield	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Inn	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

They	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
said	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
it's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
not	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
over	O	RB	UNKNOWN
...	O	IN	UNKNOWN
harvey	O	:	UNKNOWN
@	PERSON	JJ	UNKNOWN
Mosaic	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hermann	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Park	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
LIVE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
UPDATE	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Antonio	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Fatal	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
car	O	NN	UNKNOWN
accident	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Ingram	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Strong	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
winds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
Water	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
La	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Grange	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
residents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
came	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
down	O	RB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
see	O	VB	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
businesses	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
underwater	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Turkey	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Run	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
State	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
jnj	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

UPDATE	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
HFD	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
crews	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
scene	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
1100	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Block	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Bell	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Downtown	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Fire	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
appears	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Likely	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
source	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
smoke	O	NN	UNKNOWN
downtown	O	NN	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Mayor	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Search	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
operation	O	NN	UNKNOWN
underway	O	RB	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Pioneer	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Trailer	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

On	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Galveston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Seawall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
61st	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
about	O	RB	UNKNOWN
5pm	O	CD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Fri	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
25th	O	CD	UNKNOWN
August	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Galveston	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
windy	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNS	UNKNOWN

Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Arthur	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
diapers	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
babyitems	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
11	O	CD	UNKNOWN
am	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
tomorrow	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Sunday	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Joseph	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
800	O	CD	UNKNOWN
9th	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

flood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
7:00	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PM	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ELDERLY	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
CAN	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NOT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
GET	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ON	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
THE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ROOF	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NEED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
A	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RESCUE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
1230	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Havner	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
lane	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Tx	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77037	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PLEASE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SHARE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN

People	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
been	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
Rescued	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
right	O	RB	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Mason	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
rd	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
university	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
dr	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
KatyTX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Have	O	VB	UNKNOWN
some	O	DT	UNKNOWN
items	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
you'd	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
like	O	MD	UNKNOWN
to	O	VB	UNKNOWN
donate	O	TO	UNKNOWN
to	O	VB	UNKNOWN
victims	O	TO	UNKNOWN
of	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	IN	UNKNOWN
?	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
A	O	.	UNKNOWN
truck	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	NN	UNKNOWN
parked	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
off	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
I	O	IN	UNKNOWN
-	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
95	O	:	UNKNOWN
/	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Willis	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Rd	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
9010	O	(	UNKNOWN
Quinnford	O	CD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Call	O	VB	UNKNOWN
your	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
reps	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Tell	O	VB	UNKNOWN
them	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
refuse	O	VB	UNKNOWN
allocation	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
pointless	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
U.S.	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
border	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Funds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
buildings	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
still	O	RB	UNKNOWN
standing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Rowe	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Cedar	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Rose	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Goliad	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
State	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
closed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
because	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Greetings	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Fairmont	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
East	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
La	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Porte	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Anyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
know	O	VB	UNKNOWN
anything	O	NN	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
westwood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
tamina	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
rd	O	NN	UNKNOWN
2978	O	CD	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
1488	O	CD	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN

Come	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Joe	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
where	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
helping	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
RedCross	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
collect	O	NN	UNKNOWN
donations	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Aransas	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pass	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
police	ORGANIZATION	NNS	UNKNOWN
post	ORGANIZATION	VBD	UNKNOWN
video	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
town's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harbor	O	POS	UNKNOWN
Master	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Building	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
being	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
destroyed	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
by	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	IN	UNKNOWN
...	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
funding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
should	O	MD	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
allocated	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
rebuilding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
gulf	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
region	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Good	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
map	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Flashflood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
--	O	:	UNKNOWN
Alley	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
county	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
high	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
rates	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
during	O	IN	UNKNOWN
heavy	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
rains	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
via	O	IN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

CAT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
makes	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
landfall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Jose	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Island	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Those	O	DT	UNKNOWN
areas	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
ground	O	NN	UNKNOWN
zero	O	CD	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
strongest	O	JJS	UNKNOWN
part	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN

HURRICANE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HARVEY	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Damages	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Buildings	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
10	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Injured	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
20,000	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Stranded	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cruise	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ships	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Gulf	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	LOCATION	IN	UNKNOWN
Mexico	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

chainedDogs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
bird	O	NN	UNKNOWN
@	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
805	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Pennsylvania	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
SouthHouston	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
SOS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
abandoned	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
since	O	IN	UNKNOWN
last	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
week	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harveypets	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
friends	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
United	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Way	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	LOCATION	IN	UNKNOWN
Metropolitan	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dallas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
have	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
set	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
dedicated	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
fund	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
relief	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Paddling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
lives	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
corner	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Braesmont	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Braeswood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Blvd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
sxsw	O	NN	UNKNOWN

harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
Can't	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
get	O	RB	UNKNOWN
hold	O	VB	UNKNOWN
of	O	VB	UNKNOWN
our	O	IN	UNKNOWN
gran	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
on	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Cactus	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Fulton	O	IN	UNKNOWN
-	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
can	O	:	UNKNOWN
anyone	O	MD	UNKNOWN
local	O	NN	UNKNOWN
tell	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
me	O	VB	UNKNOWN
what's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
going	O	WP	UNKNOWN
on	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
there	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
?	O	IN	UNKNOWN
stormharve	O	EX	UNKNOWN

Northwest	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
hitting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
hitting	O	NN	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Category	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Your	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
forecast	O	NN	UNKNOWN
after	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Chiefs	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
game	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

UPDATED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
️	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HARVEY	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
DONATIONS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
️	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Valhalla	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Fire	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
District	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Headquarters	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
330	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Columbus	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Valhalla	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
NY	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
[	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Thomas	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
...	O	:	UNKNOWN

BREAKING	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
back	O	RB	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
coming	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
land	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
brace	O	NN	UNKNOWN
yourselves	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
going	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
church	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Annaville	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
handing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
food	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
supplies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
address	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
13024	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Leopard	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
ANIMALS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
PETS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
TAMU	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
veterinary	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
team	O	NN	UNKNOWN
locations	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Rockport	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Co	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Animal	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
361-790-0151	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
872	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Airport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

These	O	DT	UNKNOWN
clinics	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
closed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
Victoria	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Walk-In	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Twin	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Fountains	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Urgent	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Care	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lavaca	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN

Pls	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
/	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
share	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
friend's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
family	O	POS	UNKNOWN
is	O	NN	UNKNOWN
stuck	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
in	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
the	O	IN	UNKNOWN
house	O	DT	UNKNOWN
and	O	NN	UNKNOWN
water	O	CC	UNKNOWN
is	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rising	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
quickly	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
!	O	RB	UNKNOWN
2405	O	.	UNKNOWN
International	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Orange	O	,	UNKNOWN
,	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tx	O	,	UNKNOWN
77632	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	CD	UNKNOWN

Pier	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
behind	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Ocean	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
next	O	IN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Palmetto	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
stxwx	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Volunteers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Troup	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
launch	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
boat	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Rockport	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Begins	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Long	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Road	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Recovery	O	VB	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

STL	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Friends	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
Pet	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Week	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Partners	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Can	O	VB	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
spare	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
supplies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
1705	O	CD	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hanley	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
collectin	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Help	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
please	O	VB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Meadville	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
houstonflood1	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rosenberg	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
where	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
road	O	NN	UNKNOWN
collapsed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
GIANT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
sinkhole	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
right	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
outside	O	IN	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
liquor	O	NN	UNKNOWN
store	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
WTH	O	UH	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	O	NN	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
portion	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Staples	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
houston	LOCATION	JJ	UNKNOWN
city	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
hall	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Taqueria	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Garibaldi	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
closed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
power	O	NN	UNKNOWN
pole	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
down	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Flood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

My	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
friend	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
her	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
roommate	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
dogs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
attic	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
house	O	NN	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
5406	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Palm	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Dickinson	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
77539	O	CD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Alleghany	ORGANIZATION	DT	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
students	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
prep	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
donated	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
supplies	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
new	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
friends	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
who	O	WP	UNKNOWN
were	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
impacted	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

It's	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
been	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
long	O	DT	UNKNOWN
few	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
weeks	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
helping	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
the	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
team	O	DT	UNKNOWN
at	O	NN	UNKNOWN
NRG	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
manage	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
their	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
shelter	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	ORGANIZATION	NN	UNKNOWN
recovery	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
staging	ORGANIZATION	NN	UNKNOWN
operations	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
…	O	.	UNKNOWN

Im	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
19002	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Mission	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
77407	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
We	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
rescued	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonfloo	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Has	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
anyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
seen	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Strand	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
Naturally	O	RB	UNKNOWN
we	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
curious	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
what	O	WP	UNKNOWN
happending	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
23rd	O	CD	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Galveston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
sent	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
txt	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
hopefully	O	RB	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cynthia	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harmon	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
500	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Neches	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Arthur	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tx	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Stuck	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
attic	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
/	O	NN	UNKNOWN
no	O	DT	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
touch	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
blue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
sky	O	NN	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
workers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
erect	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
surge	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
leading	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Port	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
last	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
ferry	O	NN	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
d	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNS	UNKNOWN

Rockport	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
peak	O	NN	UNKNOWN
gust	O	NN	UNKNOWN
105mph	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Aransas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
pass	O	NN	UNKNOWN
116mph	O	CD	UNKNOWN
sustained	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
both	O	DT	UNKNOWN
sites	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
sub	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
Cat	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
3	O	CD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
tell	O	VB	UNKNOWN
me	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
why	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Rummel	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Creek	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Memorial	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
blks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
10	O	CD	UNKNOWN
am	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
can't	O	MD	UNKNOWN
handle	O	RB	UNKNOWN
much	O	VB	UNKNOWN
more	O	RB	UNKNOWN
rain	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	.	UNKNOWN

Richmond	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Avenue	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooded	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
between	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Edloe	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Buffalo	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Spdwy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
houston	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Plum	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Grove	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooded	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
blocked	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
BECAUSE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
OF	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Update	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
My	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
family	O	NN	UNKNOWN
STILL	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
needs	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
rescued	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
4318	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Kylewood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ct	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Arthur	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77642	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN

PORT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ARTHUR	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
SH73	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
westbound	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
LaBelle	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
CLOSED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TurnAroundDontDrown	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Elderly	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
dad	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
brother	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
daughter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
3yr	O	CD	UNKNOWN
old	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
grandson	O	NN	UNKNOWN
no	O	DT	UNKNOWN
power	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
food	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Senior	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
living	O	NN	UNKNOWN
community	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Magnolia	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Estates	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
101	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Normandy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Things	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Trump	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
thinks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
as	O	RB	UNKNOWN
important	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
include	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
hawking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
someone's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
book	O	POS	UNKNOWN
,	O	NN	UNKNOWN
winning	O	,	UNKNOWN
Missouri	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
,	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	,	UNKNOWN
border	O	CC	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
funding	O	NN	UNKNOWN

There	O	EX	UNKNOWN
were	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
volunteers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
every	O	DT	UNKNOWN
entrance	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Houston	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Astros	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
'	O	POS	UNKNOWN
Minute	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Maid	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
taking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
donations	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

"	O	``	UNKNOWN
We're	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
just	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
hour	O	RB	UNKNOWN
by	O	NN	UNKNOWN
hour	O	IN	UNKNOWN
monitoring	O	NN	UNKNOWN
everything	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	NN	UNKNOWN
"	O	,	UNKNOWN
spokesman	O	``	UNKNOWN
Cory	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Stottlemyer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
from	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Missouri	O	IN	UNKNOWN
City	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
said	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
Still	O	.	UNKNOWN
ahead	O	RB	UNKNOWN
long	O	RB	UNKNOWN
road	O	RB	UNKNOWN
ahead	O	NN	UNKNOWN
...	O	RB	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	:	UNKNOWN

Tomorrow	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
last	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
day	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
donate	O	VB	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Westminster	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Presbyterian	ORGANIZATION	JJ	UNKNOWN
Church	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Sets	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Up	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Donation	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Trailer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

URGENT	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Animal	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Animals	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Whites	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pavilion	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
10	O	CD	UNKNOWN
exit	O	NN	UNKNOWN
61	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Anahuac	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
tx	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflooding	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
FoxNews	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
aspca	O	NN	UNKNOWN
CajunNav	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

*	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
*	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
*	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
PLS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SHARE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
police	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
socks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
undershirts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
underwear	O	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
1602	O	CD	UNKNOWN
State	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
Union	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

TxDOT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Crews	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
closing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
FM	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
1322	O	CD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Plum	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Creek	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
FM	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
1854	O	CD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Highland	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ranch	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Way	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
due	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
road	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Southwest	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Calvary	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Baptist	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Church	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
open	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
12910	O	CD	UNKNOWN
W	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bellfort	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

fox26	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN
huge	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Flooding	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Mary	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bates	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Concho	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

PrayForPortA	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NN	UNKNOWN
around	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Roberts	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Point	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Port	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

PHOTOS	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Dozens	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
wait	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
line	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
into	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
HEB	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Old	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Spanish	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Trail	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Scotts	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Families	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
wait	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
stock	O	NN	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
more	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Free	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
sandbags	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
city	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
San	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Marcos	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
armory	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
wonderful	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
putting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
them	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
together	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey201	PERSON	VB	UNKNOWN

As	O	IN	UNKNOWN
seen	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
along	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Sabine	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bridge	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Had	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
out	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
house	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Water's	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
highest	O	POS	UNKNOWN
I've	O	JJS	UNKNOWN
seen	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
(	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Eldridge	O	(	UNKNOWN
park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

we'd	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
love	O	MD	UNKNOWN
2	O	VB	UNKNOWN
have	O	CD	UNKNOWN
you	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
stop	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
by	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
Sunland	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Mall	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
El	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Paso	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
today	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	NN	UNKNOWN
our	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
relief	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
drive	O	NN	UNKNOWN
today	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Anyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Misty	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Winds	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
trailer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
know	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
damage	O	NN	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN

Friends	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
mine	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
their	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
parents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
staying	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
put	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
describe	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
drive	O	NN	UNKNOWN
thru	O	NN	UNKNOWN
lines	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
longest	O	JJS	UNKNOWN
they've	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
ever	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
seen	O	RB	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	VBN	UNKNOWN

Any	O	DT	UNKNOWN
stores	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
open	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Mills	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Armored	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
vehicles	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Seawall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Boulevard	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Galveston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
guess	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
National	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Guard	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN

Hard	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
work	O	NN	UNKNOWN
selling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
lemonade	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
friends	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
kidlife	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
notabli	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Waneka	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lake	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

Arlington	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
residents	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
send	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
aid	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
FPFD	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Repost	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
・	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
・	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
・	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
United	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Way	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
coordinating	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
recovery	O	NN	UNKNOWN
efforts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
along	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Gulf	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Coast	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Only	O	RB	UNKNOWN
one	O	CD	UNKNOWN
waterway	O	NN	UNKNOWN
out	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
bank	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
Mayde	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Creek	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Greenhouse	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Pictures	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
downed	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
trees	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
damaged	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
apartment	O	NN	UNKNOWN
building	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Airline	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Road	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Corpus	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Christi	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
less	O	JJR	UNKNOWN
than	O	IN	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
miles	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
place	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
webster	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
Condition	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Nasa	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
1	O	CD	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
El	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Camino	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Real	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

*	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
*	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
*	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
PLS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SHARE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
1602	O	CD	UNKNOWN
State	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
Union	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
police	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
socks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
undershirts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
underwear	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
!!!	O	.	UNKNOWN

Two	O	CD	UNKNOWN
police	O	NN	UNKNOWN
officers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
shot	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
north	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
downtown	O	NN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Louis	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

URGENT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
DOG	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
CAT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RESCUE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NEEDED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
BOATS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
>	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
413	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Speights	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hankamer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
TALL	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TAILS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ANIMAL	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RESCUE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HARVEY	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Tomorrow's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
the	O	POS	UNKNOWN
day	O	DT	UNKNOWN
!	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Help	O	.	UNKNOWN
the	O	VB	UNKNOWN
community	O	DT	UNKNOWN
affected	O	NN	UNKNOWN
by	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	IN	UNKNOWN
and	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
dine	O	CC	UNKNOWN
at	O	NN	UNKNOWN
our	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Krog	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Incredibly	O	RB	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
destroyed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
LaQuinta	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Inn	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
1625	O	CD	UNKNOWN
W	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
but	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Supercharger	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
works	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
perfectly	O	RB	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
"	O	``	UNKNOWN
Plz	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
ppl	ORGANIZATION	NN	UNKNOWN
affected	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

These	O	DT	UNKNOWN
kids	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Heritage	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Baptist	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Church	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
came	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
college	O	NN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
families	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Dickinson	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
clean	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
debris	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
as	O	RB	UNKNOWN
far	O	RB	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
can	O	MD	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Old	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Sour	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lake	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Just	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
past	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Moore	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
SETXNews	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
does	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
anyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
know	O	VB	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
conditions	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
around	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Cypress	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ridge	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
High	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
School	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HarveyFloo	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

PET	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RESCUE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NEEDED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
20	O	CD	UNKNOWN
+	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Animals	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
413	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Speights	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Road	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Hankamer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77560	O	CD	UNKNOWN
|	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(281)-851-2500	O	(	UNKNOWN
|	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Harvey2017	O	)	UNKNOWN
HoustonStrong	O	CD	UNKNOWN
PLS	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
R	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Pls	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
RETWEET	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
>	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
>	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
>	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Animals	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
trapped	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Tall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tales	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rescue	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
send	O	NN	UNKNOWN
boats	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
please	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
413	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Speights	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
Loop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hankamer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
7756	O	CD	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Water	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Everywhere	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Playground	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
meyerland	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Godwin	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
park	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Kolter	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Elem	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Right	O	RB	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
can	O	MD	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
coming	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
1800	O	CD	UNKNOWN
N	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Lamar	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
donating	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
these	O	DT	UNKNOWN
items	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
We	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
until	O	IN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Running	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
out	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
room	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Terry	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hershey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
news	O	NN	UNKNOWN
tip	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Go	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Goose	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Island	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
State	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
see	O	VB	UNKNOWN
if	O	IN	UNKNOWN
"	O	``	UNKNOWN
The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Big	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tree	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
"	O	``	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
down	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
It	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
rode	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
every	O	DT	UNKNOWN
other	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
hurricane	O	NN	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
800	O	CD	UNKNOWN
+	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
yrs	O	NN	UNKNOWN

I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
stopped	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Walnut	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hill	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rec	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Center	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
talk	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
some	O	DT	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
evacuees	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
who've	O	WP	UNKNOWN
come	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
to	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
Dallas	O	TO	UNKNOWN
…	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN

A	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Local	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
mall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Deer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
tried	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
3x	O	CD	UNKNOWN
prices	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
customers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
aka	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
price	O	NN	UNKNOWN
gouge	O	NN	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
after	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
until	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
resident's	O	NN	UNKNOWN
complaint	O	POS	UNKNOWN
went	O	NN	UNKNOWN
viral	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
.	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Oopsies	O	.	UNKNOWN

this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
Roseland	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
baytown	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
resource	O	NN	UNKNOWN
The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Woodlands	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Church	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
295	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Sawdust	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Spring	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77380	O	CD	UNKNOWN
(281)-292-1798	O	(	UNKNOWN
Pls	O	CD	UNKNOWN
RT	O	)	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	CD	UNKNOWN
shelte	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

It	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
still	O	RB	UNKNOWN
raining	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
but	O	CC	UNKNOWN
my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
Willow	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Village	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
neighborhood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
no	O	DT	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
yet	O	RB	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Allen	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Parkway	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
dog	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
park	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
completely	O	RB	UNKNOWN
submerged	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
All	O	PDT	UNKNOWN
that	O	DT	UNKNOWN
work	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Gone	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

League	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
City	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
worked	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
large	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
house	O	NN	UNKNOWN
fire	O	NN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
afternoon	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
300	O	CD	UNKNOWN
block	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Marina	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Oaks	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ct	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
but	O	CC	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
couldn	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
’	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
t	O	NN	UNKNOWN
reach	O	NN	UNKNOWN
that	O	IN	UNKNOWN
side	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
town	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Inns	O	NN	UNKNOWN
From	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
La	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Quinta	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
refusing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
honor	O	VB	UNKNOWN
FEMA	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
vouchers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
who've	O	WP	UNKNOWN
made	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
reservations	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
with	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
them	O	IN	UNKNOWN
.	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	.	UNKNOWN
badservic	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

If	O	IN	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
see	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
road	O	NN	UNKNOWN
closures	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
due	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
please	O	VB	UNKNOWN
report	O	VB	UNKNOWN
it	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN

Janie	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Durbin	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Launches	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Florida	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Flood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Aid	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Y'all	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
This	O	DT	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
picture	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Katrina	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
thought	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
I	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
recognized	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
Canal	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonFlood	O	NN	UNKNOWN

The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
other	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
end	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Saums	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Select	O	VB	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
specific	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
county	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
East	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
or	O	CC	UNKNOWN
allow	O	VB	UNKNOWN
United	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Way	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
distribute	O	VB	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
funds	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
where	O	WRB	UNKNOWN
they	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
most	O	RBS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
…	O	VB	UNKNOWN

Signs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
home	O	NN	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Whitecap	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Boulevard	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey's	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
wake	O	POS	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
HarveyStorm	O	.	UNKNOWN
stxwx	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

my	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
church	O	NN	UNKNOWN
has	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
just	O	RB	UNKNOWN
opened	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
shelter	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
8503	O	CD	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Kirkwood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77099	O	CD	UNKNOWN
RETWEET	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
AND	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
SPREAD	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
AWARENESS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Wheeler	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Avenue	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Aransas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pass	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Stxwx	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

We	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
ok	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
here	O	RB	UNKNOWN
so	O	RB	UNKNOWN
far	O	RB	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Granite	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
between	O	IN	UNKNOWN
290	O	CD	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Hempstead	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Bingle	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Praying	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
everyone	O	NN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
ho	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Strong	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
persistent	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Western	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ridge	O	NN	UNKNOWN
bringing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
CA	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
heatwave	O	NN	UNKNOWN
may	O	MD	UNKNOWN
contribute	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
stalling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
extreme	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

TX	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
We're	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
hosting	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Town	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Meeting	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
with	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
League	O	IN	UNKNOWN
City	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
tonight	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	NN	UNKNOWN
6pm.Check	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Town	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tab	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
:	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

NEWS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ASAP	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Horse	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Trailer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
needed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
4	O	CD	UNKNOWN
horses	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Call	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Rachael	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
832-482-7603	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
5005	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Lord	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Cosby	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

fox26	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN
houwx	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Flooding	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Mary	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bates	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Concho	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Because	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Holiday	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Inn	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Express	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Suites	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Katy	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
i	O	NN	UNKNOWN
will	O	MD	UNKNOWN
never	O	RB	UNKNOWN
stay	O	VB	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
you	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
dogs	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
family	O	NN	UNKNOWN
too	O	RB	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Anyone	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
doing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
high	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rescues	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Pasadena B-location	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
/	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Deer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
area	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
?	O	NN	UNKNOWN
My	O	.	UNKNOWN
daughter	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
has	O	NN	UNKNOWN
been	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
stranded	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
a	O	IN	UNKNOWN
parking	O	DT	UNKNOWN
lot	O	NN	UNKNOWN
all	O	NN	UNKNOWN
night	O	DT	UNKNOWN

The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
back	O	NN	UNKNOWN
eye	O	NN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
nearing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
hour	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Reports	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
several	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
collapses	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
including	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
one	O	CD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Rockport	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
H	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

9013	O	CD	UNKNOWN
McGallion	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77022	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Starting	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
10am	O	CD	UNKNOWN
ALL	O	DT	UNKNOWN
WEEK	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
All	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
baby	O	NN	UNKNOWN
products	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
food	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
clothing	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
cleanin	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Smithtown	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Families	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
..	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Superior	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ice	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rink	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
is	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
working	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
those	O	DT	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
effected	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

3	O	CD	UNKNOWN
women	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
stranded	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
8130	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Snowden	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77028	O	CD	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
harvey	PERSON	VBZ	UNKNOWN
houston	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN
texas	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	VB	UNKNOWN
start	O	NN	UNKNOWN
UNUSED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
GIFT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
CARD	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
initiatives	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Send	O	VB	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Bayou	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Animal	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Services	O	NNPS	UNKNOWN
3120	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Deats	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Dickinson	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Texas	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
...	O	:	UNKNOWN

Kimberley	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Beltway	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
8	O	CD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Who	O	WP	UNKNOWN
put	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
sign	O	NN	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
Wow	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
strange	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
sense	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
humor	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Neighborhood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
storm	O	NN	UNKNOWN
drains	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Nederland	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
already	O	RB	UNKNOWN
busy	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
handling	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
accumulation	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
spotty	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
rain	O	NN	UNKNOWN
bursts	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	PERSON	NN	UNKNOWN

tomorrow	O	NN	UNKNOWN
morning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
8am	O	CD	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Garden	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
City	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Salvation	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Army	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Boys	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
Girls	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
9717	ORGANIZATION	CD	UNKNOWN
West	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Montgomery	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN

ELDERLY	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
COUPLE	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
WITH	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
WATER	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
UP	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
TO	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
THEIR	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
NECKS	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
NEED	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HELP	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
7605	O	CD	UNKNOWN
9th	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
PortArthur	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HarveyStorm	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Donations	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
bottled	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
water	O	NN	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
diapers	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
can	O	MD	UNKNOWN
be	O	VB	UNKNOWN
dropped	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
off	O	IN	UNKNOWN
between	O	IN	UNKNOWN
9	O	CD	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
m	O	NN	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
9	O	CD	UNKNOWN
p	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
m	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Burbank	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Fire	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Station	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(8	O	(	UNKNOWN
455	O	CD	UNKNOWN
S	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Mayfield	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ave	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
)	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harve	O	)	UNKNOWN

Convoy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HEB	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
trucks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
headed	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
north	O	RB	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Louisiana	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
harvey	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN

Buffalo	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Bayou	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
S	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Piney	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Point	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
crossable	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
2:00	O	CD	UNKNOWN
pm	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
about	O	IN	UNKNOWN
2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
feet	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
bridge	O	NN	UNKNOWN
KPRC2	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
houstonflood	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Can't	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
focus	O	RB	UNKNOWN
on	O	VB	UNKNOWN
writing	O	IN	UNKNOWN
so	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
decided	O	RB	UNKNOWN
to	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
donate	O	TO	UNKNOWN
blood	O	VB	UNKNOWN
.	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Praying	O	.	UNKNOWN
for	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
those	O	IN	UNKNOWN
affected	O	DT	UNKNOWN
by	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	IN	UNKNOWN
.	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
TeXas	O	.	UNKNOWN
has	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
long	O	DT	UNKNOWN
road	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
ahead	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	RB	UNKNOWN

Donations	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
meal	O	NN	UNKNOWN
located	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
240	O	CD	UNKNOWN
W	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
18th	O	CD	UNKNOWN
St	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
77008	O	CD	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
Fellowship	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
114Actsofservice	O	CD	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarve	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Come	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
help	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
us	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
out	O	RP	UNKNOWN
rayford	O	NN	UNKNOWN
rd	O	NN	UNKNOWN
by	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Kroger	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
we	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
need	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
all	O	PDT	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
we	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
can	O	MD	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	VB	UNKNOWN

City	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Beaumont	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
giving	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
away	O	RB	UNKNOWN
up	O	IN	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
16	O	CD	UNKNOWN
sandbags	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
per	O	IN	UNKNOWN
car	O	NN	UNKNOWN
over	O	IN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
2610	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Concord	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
ahead	O	RB	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Drop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
the	O	DT	UNKNOWN
damned	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
wall	O	NN	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
divert	O	VB	UNKNOWN
those	O	DT	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
$	O	$	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
help	O	VB	UNKNOWN
HoustonFloods	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
victims	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
&	O	CC	UNKNOWN
rebuild	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Southeast	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
infrastruct	O	NN	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Watterson	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
rd	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Donation	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
station	O	NN	UNKNOWN
In	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Bastrop	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
City	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

2	O	CD	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
need	O	NN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
rescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
Bavaria	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
buildings	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
12431	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Maura	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Lane	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77044.	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Near	O	.	UNKNOWN
CE	O	IN	UNKNOWN
King	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pkwy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Tidwell	O	CC	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
HarveySO	O	NNP	UNKNOWN

Mayor	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
says	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
PortAransas	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
trailer	O	NN	UNKNOWN
park	O	NN	UNKNOWN
100	O	CD	UNKNOWN
%	O	NN	UNKNOWN
loss	O	NN	UNKNOWN
prayers	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
up	O	RP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN

Local	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Way	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Donate	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
HurricaneHarvey:	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Native	O	:	UNKNOWN
Hostel	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
Donation	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Drive	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
DJ	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Set	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
-	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
365	O	:	UNKNOWN
Things	O	CD	UNKNOWN
to	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
Do	O	TO	UNKNOWN
in	O	VB	UNKNOWN
Austin	O	IN	UNKNOWN
,	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
TX	O	,	UNKNOWN

8305	O	CD	UNKNOWN
talton	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
street	O	NN	UNKNOWN
houston	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
tx	LOCATION	SYM	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
-	O	:	UNKNOWN
did	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
they	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
get	O	VB	UNKNOWN
rescued	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
?	O	.	UNKNOWN
HoustonFloods	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
news	O	NN	UNKNOWN
kid	O	NN	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
ventilator	O	NN	UNKNOWN

80	O	CD	UNKNOWN
people	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
stranded	O	VBN	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
a	O	DT	UNKNOWN
church	O	NN	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
5547	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Cavalcade	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
TX	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
77026	O	CD	UNKNOWN
harveyrescue	O	NN	UNKNOWN
hurricaneharvey	O	NN	UNKNOWN
sendhelp	O	NN	UNKNOWN
harveysos	O	VB	UNKNOWN
houston	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN
texa	LOCATION	NN	UNKNOWN

The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
mobile	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
health	O	NN	UNKNOWN
teams	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
are	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
seeing	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
evacuees	O	VBZ	UNKNOWN
@	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Toney	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Burger	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Activity	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Ctr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
(	O	(	UNKNOWN
3200	O	CD	UNKNOWN
Jones	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
)	O	)	UNKNOWN
C	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
…	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Irma	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
CAT	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
5	O	CD	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
now	O	RB	UNKNOWN
near	O	IN	UNKNOWN
St	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Thomas	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
185mph	O	CD	UNKNOWN
wind	O	NN	UNKNOWN
;	O	:	UNKNOWN
Aquaivia	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
From	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Hurricane	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Irma	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
;	O	:	UNKNOWN
Houston	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
Miami	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Please	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
reTweet	O	NN	UNKNOWN

The	O	DT	UNKNOWN
view	O	NN	UNKNOWN
from	O	IN	UNKNOWN
our	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
apt	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
roof	O	VB	UNKNOWN
looking	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Spotts	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Park	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
Waugh	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
and	O	CC	UNKNOWN
Memorial	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Dr	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
,	O	,	UNKNOWN
as	O	IN	UNKNOWN
of	O	IN	UNKNOWN
this	O	DT	UNKNOWN
morning	O	NN	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Harvey	PERSON	VB	UNKNOWN

NOLAReady	O	JJ	UNKNOWN
alert	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
Street	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
flooding	O	NN	UNKNOWN
reported	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
at	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Bienville	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
St	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
and	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
N	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Jeff	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Davis	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Pkwy	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	O	.	UNKNOWN
Visit	O	NN	UNKNOWN

Thanks	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Home	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Depot	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Plano	LOCATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
on	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Custer	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Rd	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
for	O	IN	UNKNOWN
your	O	PRP$	UNKNOWN
help	O	NN	UNKNOWN
with	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Flood	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Cleanup	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Kits	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
!	O	.	UNKNOWN
Pray	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
they	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
sent	O	VBD	UNKNOWN
folks	O	NNS	UNKNOWN
to	O	TO	UNKNOWN
…	O	VB	UNKNOWN

TX	O	NN	UNKNOWN
:	O	:	UNKNOWN
We're	O	PRP	UNKNOWN
hosting	O	VBP	UNKNOWN
a	O	VBG	UNKNOWN
Harvey	O	DT	UNKNOWN
Town	PERSON	NNP	UNKNOWN
Hall	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
Meeting	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
with	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
in	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Friendswood	O	IN	UNKNOWN
Co	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	.	UNKNOWN
League	O	,	UNKNOWN
City	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
,	O	NNP	UNKNOWN
&	O	,	UNKNOWN
Dickson	ORGANIZATION	CC	UNKNOWN
Co	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
.	ORGANIZATION	NNP	UNKNOWN
Info	O	.	UNKNOWN
:	O	NN	UNKNOWN
